{"H_COMP_1":{"H_COMP_1_A_P":{"id":"H_COMP_1_A_P","question":"Patients who reported that their nurses Always communicated well","answer":"Nurses always communicated well","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"55":1,"58":1,"59":1,"60":1,"61":1,"62":1,"63":1,"64":1,"65":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"97":1,"98":1,"99":1,"100":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_COMP_1_SN_P":{"id":"H_COMP_1_SN_P","question":"Patients who reported that their nurses Sometimes or Never communicated well","answer":"Nurses sometimes or never communicated well","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"22":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_COMP_1_U_P":{"id":"H_COMP_1_U_P","question":"Patients who reported that their nurses Usually communicated well","answer":"Nurses usually communicated well","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"29":1,"31":1,"32":1,"33":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_COMP_1_LINEAR_SCORE":{"id":"H_COMP_1_LINEAR_SCORE","question":"Nurse communication - linear mean score","answer":"Nurse communication - linear mean score","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"97":1,"98":1,"":1}},"H_COMP_1_STAR_RATING":{"id":"H_COMP_1_STAR_RATING","question":"Nurse communication - star rating","answer":"Nurse communication - star rating","patientSurveyStarRating":{"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_NURSE_RESPECT":{"H_NURSE_RESPECT_A_P":{"id":"H_NURSE_RESPECT_A_P","question":"Patients who reported that their nurses Always treated them with courtesy and respect","answer":"Nurses always treated them with courtesy and  respect","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"97":1,"98":1,"99":1,"100":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_NURSE_RESPECT_SN_P":{"id":"H_NURSE_RESPECT_SN_P","question":"Patients who reported that their nurses Sometimes or Never  treated them with courtesy and respect","answer":"Nurses sometimes or never treated them with courtesy and  respect","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"17":1,"19":1,"21":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_NURSE_RESPECT_U_P":{"id":"H_NURSE_RESPECT_U_P","question":"Patients who reported that their nurses Usually  treated them with courtesy and respect","answer":"Nurses usually  treated them with courtesy and  respect","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"28":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_NURSE_LISTEN":{"H_NURSE_LISTEN_A_P":{"id":"H_NURSE_LISTEN_A_P","question":"Patients who reported that their nurses Always listened carefully to them","answer":"Nurses always listened carefully","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"52":1,"54":1,"55":1,"56":1,"57":1,"59":1,"60":1,"61":1,"62":1,"63":1,"64":1,"65":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"97":1,"100":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_NURSE_LISTEN_SN_P":{"id":"H_NURSE_LISTEN_SN_P","question":"Patients who reported that their nurses Sometimes or Never listened carefully to them","answer":"Nurses sometimes or never listened carefully","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"25":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_NURSE_LISTEN_U_P":{"id":"H_NURSE_LISTEN_U_P","question":"Patients who reported that their nurses Usually listened carefully to them","answer":"Nurses usually listened carefully","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"37":1,"40":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_NURSE_EXPLAIN":{"H_NURSE_EXPLAIN_A_P":{"id":"H_NURSE_EXPLAIN_A_P","question":"Patients who reported that their nurses Always explained things in a way they could understand","answer":"Nurses always explained things so they could understand","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"54":1,"55":1,"56":1,"57":1,"58":1,"59":1,"60":1,"61":1,"62":1,"63":1,"64":1,"65":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"98":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_NURSE_EXPLAIN_SN_P":{"id":"H_NURSE_EXPLAIN_SN_P","question":"Patients who reported that their nurses Sometimes or Never explained things in a way they could understand","answer":"Nurses sometimes or never explained things so they could understand","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_NURSE_EXPLAIN_U_P":{"id":"H_NURSE_EXPLAIN_U_P","question":"Patients who reported that their nurses Usually explained things in a way they could understand","answer":"Nurses usually explained things so they could understand","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"32":1,"33":1,"34":1,"38":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_COMP_2":{"H_COMP_2_A_P":{"id":"H_COMP_2_A_P","question":"Patients who reported that their doctors Always communicated well","answer":"Doctors always communicated well","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"52":1,"58":1,"59":1,"60":1,"61":1,"62":1,"63":1,"64":1,"65":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"97":1,"98":1,"99":1,"100":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_COMP_2_SN_P":{"id":"H_COMP_2_SN_P","question":"Patients who reported that their doctors Sometimes or Never communicated well","answer":"Doctors sometimes or never communicated well","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"18":1,"19":1,"21":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_COMP_2_U_P":{"id":"H_COMP_2_U_P","question":"Patients who reported that their doctors Usually communicated well","answer":"Doctors usually communicated well","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"39":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_COMP_2_LINEAR_SCORE":{"id":"H_COMP_2_LINEAR_SCORE","question":"Doctor communication - linear mean score","answer":"Doctor communication - linear mean score","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"78":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"97":1,"98":1,"99":1,"100":1,"":1}},"H_COMP_2_STAR_RATING":{"id":"H_COMP_2_STAR_RATING","question":"Doctor communication - star rating","answer":"Doctor communication - star rating","patientSurveyStarRating":{"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_DOCTOR_RESPECT":{"H_DOCTOR_RESPECT_A_P":{"id":"H_DOCTOR_RESPECT_A_P","question":"Patients who reported that their doctors Always treated them with courtesy and respect","answer":"Doctors always treated them with courtesy and  respect","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"97":1,"98":1,"99":1,"100":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_DOCTOR_RESPECT_SN_P":{"id":"H_DOCTOR_RESPECT_SN_P","question":"Patients who reported that their doctors Sometimes or Never  treated them with courtesy and respect","answer":"Doctors sometimes or never treated them with courtesy and  respect","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"17":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_DOCTOR_RESPECT_U_P":{"id":"H_DOCTOR_RESPECT_U_P","question":"Patients who reported that their doctors Usually  treated them with courtesy and respect","answer":"Doctors usually  treated them with courtesy and  respect","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_DOCTOR_LISTEN":{"H_DOCTOR_LISTEN_A_P":{"id":"H_DOCTOR_LISTEN_A_P","question":"Patients who reported that their doctors Always listened carefully to them","answer":"Doctors always listened carefully","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"58":1,"59":1,"61":1,"62":1,"63":1,"64":1,"65":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"97":1,"98":1,"99":1,"100":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_DOCTOR_LISTEN_SN_P":{"id":"H_DOCTOR_LISTEN_SN_P","question":"Patients who reported that their doctors Sometimes or Never listened carefully to them","answer":"Doctors sometimes or never listened carefully","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"21":1,"22":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_DOCTOR_LISTEN_U_P":{"id":"H_DOCTOR_LISTEN_U_P","question":"Patients who reported that their doctors Usually listened carefully to them","answer":"Doctors usually listened carefully","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"32":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_DOCTOR_EXPLAIN":{"H_DOCTOR_EXPLAIN_A_P":{"id":"H_DOCTOR_EXPLAIN_A_P","question":"Patients who reported that their doctors Always explained things in a way they could understand","answer":"Doctors always explained things so they could understand","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"55":1,"56":1,"57":1,"58":1,"59":1,"60":1,"61":1,"62":1,"63":1,"64":1,"65":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"97":1,"98":1,"99":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_DOCTOR_EXPLAIN_SN_P":{"id":"H_DOCTOR_EXPLAIN_SN_P","question":"Patients who reported that their doctors Sometimes or Never explained things in a way they could understand","answer":"Doctors sometimes or never explained things so they could understand","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_DOCTOR_EXPLAIN_U_P":{"id":"H_DOCTOR_EXPLAIN_U_P","question":"Patients who reported that their doctors Usually explained things in a way they could understand","answer":"Doctors usually explained things so they could understand","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"32":1,"34":1,"36":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_COMP_3":{"H_COMP_3_A_P":{"id":"H_COMP_3_A_P","question":"Patients who reported that they Always received help as soon as they wanted","answer":"Patients always received help as soon as they wanted","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"29":1,"37":1,"38":1,"39":1,"42":1,"43":1,"44":1,"45":1,"46":1,"47":1,"48":1,"49":1,"50":1,"51":1,"52":1,"53":1,"54":1,"55":1,"56":1,"57":1,"58":1,"59":1,"60":1,"61":1,"62":1,"63":1,"64":1,"65":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"97":1,"98":1,"99":1,"100":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_COMP_3_SN_P":{"id":"H_COMP_3_SN_P","question":"Patients who reported that they Sometimes or Never received help as soon as they wanted","answer":"Patients sometimes or never received help as soon as they wanted","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"32":1,"33":1,"34":1,"36":1,"38":1,"40":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_COMP_3_U_P":{"id":"H_COMP_3_U_P","question":"Patients who reported that they Usually received help as soon as they wanted","answer":"Patients usually received help as soon as they wanted","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"32":1,"33":1,"34":1,"35":1,"36":1,"37":1,"38":1,"39":1,"40":1,"41":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_COMP_3_LINEAR_SCORE":{"id":"H_COMP_3_LINEAR_SCORE","question":"Staff responsiveness - linear mean score","answer":"Staff responsiveness - linear mean score","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"65":1,"67":1,"68":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"97":1,"98":1,"99":1,"":1}},"H_COMP_3_STAR_RATING":{"id":"H_COMP_3_STAR_RATING","question":"Staff responsiveness - star rating","answer":"Staff responsiveness - star rating","patientSurveyStarRating":{"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_CALL_BUTTON":{"H_CALL_BUTTON_A_P":{"id":"H_CALL_BUTTON_A_P","question":"Patients who reported that they Always received help after using the call button as soon as they wanted","answer":"Patients always received call button help as soon as they wanted","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"32":1,"34":1,"35":1,"38":1,"40":1,"41":1,"42":1,"43":1,"44":1,"45":1,"46":1,"47":1,"48":1,"49":1,"50":1,"51":1,"52":1,"53":1,"54":1,"55":1,"56":1,"57":1,"58":1,"59":1,"60":1,"61":1,"62":1,"63":1,"64":1,"65":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"97":1,"99":1,"100":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_CALL_BUTTON_SN_P":{"id":"H_CALL_BUTTON_SN_P","question":"Patients who reported that they Sometimes or Never received help after using the call button as soon as they wanted","answer":"Patients sometimes or never received call button help as soon as they wanted","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"32":1,"33":1,"34":1,"35":1,"37":1,"41":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_CALL_BUTTON_U_P":{"id":"H_CALL_BUTTON_U_P","question":"Patients who reported that they Usually received help after using the call button as soon as they wanted","answer":"Patients usually received call button help as soon as they wanted","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"32":1,"33":1,"34":1,"35":1,"36":1,"37":1,"38":1,"39":1,"40":1,"41":1,"42":1,"45":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_BATH_HELP":{"H_BATH_HELP_A_P":{"id":"H_BATH_HELP_A_P","question":"Patients who reported that they Always received bathroom help as soon as they wanted","answer":"Patients always received bathroom help as soon as they wanted","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"39":1,"41":1,"42":1,"44":1,"46":1,"47":1,"48":1,"49":1,"50":1,"51":1,"52":1,"53":1,"54":1,"55":1,"56":1,"57":1,"58":1,"59":1,"60":1,"61":1,"62":1,"63":1,"64":1,"65":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"98":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_BATH_HELP_SN_P":{"id":"H_BATH_HELP_SN_P","question":"Patients who reported that they Sometimes or Never received bathroom help as soon as they wanted","answer":"Patients sometimes or never received bathroom help as soon as they wanted","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"32":1,"34":1,"37":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_BATH_HELP_U_P":{"id":"H_BATH_HELP_U_P","question":"Patients who reported that they Usually received bathroom help as soon as they wanted","answer":"Patients usually received bathroom help as soon as they wanted","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"32":1,"33":1,"34":1,"35":1,"36":1,"37":1,"38":1,"39":1,"40":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_COMP_5":{"H_COMP_5_A_P":{"id":"H_COMP_5_A_P","question":"Patients who reported that staff Always explained about medicines before giving it to them","answer":"Staff always explained","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"15":1,"23":1,"31":1,"39":1,"40":1,"41":1,"42":1,"43":1,"45":1,"46":1,"47":1,"48":1,"49":1,"50":1,"51":1,"52":1,"53":1,"54":1,"55":1,"56":1,"57":1,"58":1,"59":1,"60":1,"61":1,"62":1,"63":1,"64":1,"65":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"96":1,"97":1,"100":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_COMP_5_SN_P":{"id":"H_COMP_5_SN_P","question":"Patients who reported that staff Sometimes or Never explained about medicines before giving it to them","answer":"Staff sometimes or never explained","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"32":1,"33":1,"34":1,"35":1,"37":1,"38":1,"39":1,"40":1,"45":1,"47":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_COMP_5_U_P":{"id":"H_COMP_5_U_P","question":"Patients who reported that staff Usually explained about medicines before giving it to them","answer":"Staff usually explained","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"32":1,"33":1,"34":1,"35":1,"36":1,"37":1,"38":1,"47":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_COMP_5_LINEAR_SCORE":{"id":"H_COMP_5_LINEAR_SCORE","question":"Communication about medicines - linear mean score","answer":"Communication about medicines - linear mean score","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"59":1,"62":1,"64":1,"65":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"97":1,"99":1,"":1}},"H_COMP_5_STAR_RATING":{"id":"H_COMP_5_STAR_RATING","question":"Communication about medicines - star rating","answer":"Communication about medicines - star rating","patientSurveyStarRating":{"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_MED_FOR":{"H_MED_FOR_A_P":{"id":"H_MED_FOR_A_P","question":"Patients who reported that when receiving new medication the staff Always communicated what the medication was for","answer":"Staff always explained new medications","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"45":1,"51":1,"53":1,"57":1,"58":1,"60":1,"61":1,"62":1,"63":1,"64":1,"65":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"97":1,"98":1,"99":1,"100":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_MED_FOR_SN_P":{"id":"H_MED_FOR_SN_P","question":"Patients who reported that when receiving new medication the staff Sometimes or Never communicated what the medication was for","answer":"Staff sometimes or never explained new medications","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"26":1,"29":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_MED_FOR_U_P":{"id":"H_MED_FOR_U_P","question":"Patients who reported that when receiving new medication the staff Usually communicated what the medication was for.","answer":"Staff usually explained new medications","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"32":1,"35":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_SIDE_EFFECTS":{"H_SIDE_EFFECTS_A_P":{"id":"H_SIDE_EFFECTS_A_P","question":"Patients who reported that when receiving new medication the staff Always discussed possible side effects","answer":"Staff always explained possible side effects","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"17":1,"23":1,"27":1,"28":1,"30":1,"33":1,"34":1,"35":1,"36":1,"37":1,"38":1,"39":1,"40":1,"41":1,"42":1,"43":1,"44":1,"45":1,"46":1,"47":1,"48":1,"49":1,"50":1,"51":1,"52":1,"53":1,"54":1,"55":1,"56":1,"57":1,"58":1,"59":1,"60":1,"61":1,"62":1,"63":1,"64":1,"65":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"88":1,"89":1,"94":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_SIDE_EFFECTS_SN_P":{"id":"H_SIDE_EFFECTS_SN_P","question":"Patients who reported that when receiving new medication the staff Sometimes or Never discussed possible side effects","answer":"Staff sometimes or never explained possible side effects","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"32":1,"33":1,"34":1,"35":1,"36":1,"37":1,"38":1,"39":1,"40":1,"41":1,"42":1,"43":1,"44":1,"45":1,"46":1,"47":1,"48":1,"49":1,"50":1,"51":1,"52":1,"55":1,"56":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_SIDE_EFFECTS_U_P":{"id":"H_SIDE_EFFECTS_U_P","question":"Patients who reported that when receiving new medication the staff Usually discussed possible side effects","answer":"Staff usually explained possible side effects","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"32":1,"33":1,"34":1,"35":1,"36":1,"37":1,"38":1,"39":1,"40":1,"41":1,"50":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_COMP_6":{"H_COMP_6_N_P":{"id":"H_COMP_6_N_P","question":"Patients who reported that NO they were not given information about what to do during their recovery at home","answer":"No staff did not give patients this information","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"32":1,"33":1,"34":1,"36":1,"41":1,"42":1,"51":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_COMP_6_Y_P":{"id":"H_COMP_6_Y_P","question":"Patients who reported that YES they were given information about what to do during their recovery at home","answer":"Yes staff did give patients this information","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"49":1,"58":1,"59":1,"64":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"97":1,"98":1,"99":1,"100":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_COMP_6_LINEAR_SCORE":{"id":"H_COMP_6_LINEAR_SCORE","question":"Discharge information - linear mean score","answer":"Discharge information - linear mean score","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"66":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"98":1,"99":1,"100":1,"":1}},"H_COMP_6_STAR_RATING":{"id":"H_COMP_6_STAR_RATING","question":"Discharge information - star rating","answer":"Discharge information - star rating","patientSurveyStarRating":{"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_DISCH_HELP":{"H_DISCH_HELP_N_P":{"id":"H_DISCH_HELP_N_P","question":"Patients who reported that NO they did not discuss whether they would need help after discharge","answer":"No staff did not give patients information about help after discharge","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"32":1,"33":1,"34":1,"35":1,"36":1,"37":1,"38":1,"42":1,"44":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_DISCH_HELP_Y_P":{"id":"H_DISCH_HELP_Y_P","question":"Patients who reported that YES they did discuss whether they would need help after discharge","answer":"Yes staff did give patients information about help after discharge","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"56":1,"58":1,"62":1,"63":1,"64":1,"65":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"97":1,"98":1,"99":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_SYMPTOMS":{"H_SYMPTOMS_N_P":{"id":"H_SYMPTOMS_N_P","question":"Patients who reported that NO they did not receive written information about possible symptoms to look out for after discharge","answer":"No staff did not give patients information about possible symptoms","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"30":1,"31":1,"36":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_SYMPTOMS_Y_P":{"id":"H_SYMPTOMS_Y_P","question":"Patients who reported that YES they did receive written information about possible symptoms to look out for after discharge","answer":"Yes staff did give patients information about possible symptoms","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"64":1,"69":1,"70":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"97":1,"98":1,"99":1,"100":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_COMP_7":{"H_COMP_7_A":{"id":"H_COMP_7_A","question":"Patients who Agree they understood their care when they left the hospital","answer":"Patients who Agree they understood their care when they left the hospital","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"4":1,"5":1,"8":1,"11":1,"12":1,"15":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"32":1,"33":1,"34":1,"35":1,"36":1,"37":1,"38":1,"39":1,"40":1,"41":1,"42":1,"43":1,"44":1,"45":1,"46":1,"47":1,"48":1,"49":1,"50":1,"51":1,"52":1,"53":1,"54":1,"55":1,"56":1,"57":1,"58":1,"59":1,"60":1,"61":1,"62":1,"66":1,"68":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_COMP_7_D_SD":{"id":"H_COMP_7_D_SD","question":"Patients who Disagree or Strongly Disagree they understood their care when they left the hospital","answer":"Patients who Disagree or Strongly Disagree they understood their care when they left the hospital","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_COMP_7_SA":{"id":"H_COMP_7_SA","question":"Patients who Strongly Agree they understood their care when they left the hospital","answer":"Patients who Strongly Agree they understood their care when they left the hospital","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"32":1,"33":1,"34":1,"35":1,"36":1,"37":1,"38":1,"39":1,"40":1,"41":1,"42":1,"43":1,"44":1,"45":1,"46":1,"47":1,"48":1,"49":1,"50":1,"51":1,"52":1,"53":1,"54":1,"55":1,"56":1,"57":1,"58":1,"59":1,"60":1,"61":1,"62":1,"63":1,"64":1,"65":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"82":1,"85":1,"86":1,"91":1,"95":1,"96":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_COMP_7_LINEAR_SCORE":{"id":"H_COMP_7_LINEAR_SCORE","question":"Care transition - linear mean score","answer":"Care transition - linear mean score","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"97":1,"98":1,"":1}},"H_COMP_7_STAR_RATING":{"id":"H_COMP_7_STAR_RATING","question":"Care transition - star rating","answer":"Care transition - star rating","patientSurveyStarRating":{"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_CT_PREFER":{"H_CT_PREFER_A":{"id":"H_CT_PREFER_A","question":"Patients who Agree that the staff took my preferences into account when determining my health care needs","answer":"Patients who Agree that staff took their preferences into account","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"4":1,"8":1,"13":1,"15":1,"20":1,"23":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"32":1,"33":1,"34":1,"35":1,"36":1,"37":1,"38":1,"39":1,"40":1,"41":1,"42":1,"43":1,"44":1,"45":1,"46":1,"47":1,"48":1,"49":1,"50":1,"51":1,"52":1,"53":1,"54":1,"55":1,"56":1,"57":1,"58":1,"59":1,"60":1,"61":1,"62":1,"63":1,"64":1,"65":1,"66":1,"69":1,"70":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_CT_PREFER_D_SD":{"id":"H_CT_PREFER_D_SD","question":"Patients who Disagree or Strongly Disagree that the staff took my preferences into account when determining my health care needs","answer":"Patients who Disagree or Strongly Disagree that staff took their preferences into account","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_CT_PREFER_SA":{"id":"H_CT_PREFER_SA","question":"Patients who Strongly Agree that the staff took my preferences into account when determining my health care needs","answer":"Patients who Strongly Agree that staff took their preferences into account","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"18":1,"21":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"32":1,"33":1,"34":1,"35":1,"36":1,"37":1,"38":1,"39":1,"40":1,"41":1,"42":1,"43":1,"44":1,"45":1,"46":1,"47":1,"48":1,"49":1,"50":1,"51":1,"52":1,"53":1,"54":1,"55":1,"56":1,"57":1,"58":1,"59":1,"60":1,"61":1,"62":1,"63":1,"64":1,"65":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"74":1,"75":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"92":1,"96":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_CT_UNDER":{"H_CT_UNDER_A":{"id":"H_CT_UNDER_A","question":"Patients who Agree that they understood their responsiblities in managing their health","answer":"Patients who Agree they understood their responsiblities when they left the hospital","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"4":1,"8":1,"9":1,"14":1,"16":1,"17":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"32":1,"33":1,"34":1,"35":1,"36":1,"37":1,"38":1,"39":1,"40":1,"41":1,"42":1,"43":1,"44":1,"45":1,"46":1,"47":1,"48":1,"49":1,"50":1,"51":1,"52":1,"53":1,"54":1,"55":1,"56":1,"57":1,"58":1,"59":1,"60":1,"61":1,"63":1,"65":1,"71":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_CT_UNDER_D_SD":{"id":"H_CT_UNDER_D_SD","question":"Patients who Disagree or Strongly Disagree that they understood their responsiblities in managing their health","answer":"Patients who Disagree or Strongly Disagree they understood their responsiblities when they left the hospital","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"18":1,"19":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_CT_UNDER_SA":{"id":"H_CT_UNDER_SA","question":"Patients who Strongly Agree that they understood their responsiblities in managing their health","answer":"Patients who Strongly Agree they understood their responsiblities when they left the hospital","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"26":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"32":1,"33":1,"34":1,"35":1,"36":1,"37":1,"38":1,"39":1,"40":1,"41":1,"42":1,"43":1,"44":1,"45":1,"46":1,"47":1,"48":1,"49":1,"50":1,"51":1,"52":1,"53":1,"54":1,"55":1,"56":1,"57":1,"58":1,"59":1,"60":1,"61":1,"62":1,"63":1,"64":1,"65":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"77":1,"81":1,"82":1,"84":1,"89":1,"92":1,"96":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_CT_MED":{"H_CT_MED_A":{"id":"H_CT_MED_A","question":"Patients who Agree that they understood the purposes of their medications when leaving the hospital","answer":"Patients who Agree they understood their medications when they left the hospital","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"2":1,"5":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"32":1,"33":1,"34":1,"35":1,"36":1,"37":1,"38":1,"39":1,"40":1,"41":1,"42":1,"43":1,"44":1,"45":1,"46":1,"47":1,"48":1,"49":1,"50":1,"51":1,"52":1,"53":1,"54":1,"55":1,"56":1,"57":1,"58":1,"59":1,"61":1,"65":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_CT_MED_D_SD":{"id":"H_CT_MED_D_SD","question":"Patients who Disagree or Strongly Disagree that they understood the purposes of their medications when leaving the hospital","answer":"Patients who Disagree or Strongly Disagree they understood their medications when they left the hospital","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"14":1,"16":1,"21":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_CT_MED_SA":{"id":"H_CT_MED_SA","question":"Patients who Strongly Agree that they understood the purposes of their medications when leaving the hospital","answer":"Patients who Strongly Agree they understood their medications when they left the hospital","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"33":1,"35":1,"36":1,"37":1,"38":1,"39":1,"40":1,"41":1,"42":1,"43":1,"44":1,"45":1,"46":1,"47":1,"48":1,"49":1,"50":1,"51":1,"52":1,"53":1,"54":1,"55":1,"56":1,"57":1,"58":1,"59":1,"60":1,"61":1,"62":1,"63":1,"64":1,"65":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"85":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"94":1,"97":1,"98":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_CLEAN":{"H_CLEAN_HSP_A_P":{"id":"H_CLEAN_HSP_A_P","question":"Patients who reported that their room and bathroom were Always clean","answer":"Room was always clean","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"38":1,"44":1,"48":1,"51":1,"52":1,"53":1,"54":1,"55":1,"56":1,"57":1,"58":1,"59":1,"60":1,"61":1,"62":1,"63":1,"64":1,"65":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"97":1,"98":1,"99":1,"100":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_CLEAN_HSP_SN_P":{"id":"H_CLEAN_HSP_SN_P","question":"Patients who reported that their room and bathroom were Sometimes or Never clean","answer":"Room was sometimes or never clean","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"30":1,"31":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_CLEAN_HSP_U_P":{"id":"H_CLEAN_HSP_U_P","question":"Patients who reported that their room and bathroom were Usually clean","answer":"Room was usually clean","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"33":1,"37":1,"41":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_CLEAN_LINEAR_SCORE":{"id":"H_CLEAN_LINEAR_SCORE","question":"Cleanliness - linear mean score","answer":"Cleanliness - linear mean score","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"73":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"97":1,"98":1,"":1}},"H_CLEAN_STAR_RATING":{"id":"H_CLEAN_STAR_RATING","question":"Cleanliness - star rating","answer":"Cleanliness - star rating","patientSurveyStarRating":{"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_QUIET":{"H_QUIET_HSP_A_P":{"id":"H_QUIET_HSP_A_P","question":"Patients who reported that the area around their room was Always quiet at night","answer":"Always quiet at night","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"28":1,"34":1,"35":1,"36":1,"37":1,"38":1,"39":1,"40":1,"41":1,"42":1,"43":1,"44":1,"45":1,"46":1,"47":1,"48":1,"49":1,"50":1,"51":1,"52":1,"53":1,"54":1,"55":1,"56":1,"57":1,"58":1,"59":1,"60":1,"61":1,"62":1,"63":1,"64":1,"65":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_QUIET_HSP_SN_P":{"id":"H_QUIET_HSP_SN_P","question":"Patients who reported that the area around their room was Sometimes or Never quiet at night","answer":"Sometimes or never quiet at night","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"33":1,"34":1,"39":1,"44":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_QUIET_HSP_U_P":{"id":"H_QUIET_HSP_U_P","question":"Patients who reported that the area around their room was Usually quiet at night","answer":"Usually quiet at night","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"32":1,"33":1,"34":1,"35":1,"36":1,"37":1,"38":1,"39":1,"40":1,"41":1,"42":1,"43":1,"44":1,"45":1,"46":1,"47":1,"48":1,"49":1,"51":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_QUIET_LINEAR_SCORE":{"id":"H_QUIET_LINEAR_SCORE","question":"Quietness - linear mean score","answer":"Quietness - linear mean score","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"55":1,"63":1,"64":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"97":1,"":1}},"H_QUIET_STAR_RATING":{"id":"H_QUIET_STAR_RATING","question":"Quietness - star rating","answer":"Quietness - star rating","patientSurveyStarRating":{"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_HSP_RATING":{"H_HSP_RATING_0_6":{"id":"H_HSP_RATING_0_6","question":"Patients who gave their hospital a rating of 6 or lower on a scale from 0 (lowest) to 10 (highest)","answer":"Patients who gave a rating of 6 or lower (low)","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"31":1,"32":1,"36":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_HSP_RATING_7_8":{"id":"H_HSP_RATING_7_8","question":"Patients who gave their hospital a rating of 7 or 8 on a scale from 0 (lowest) to 10 (highest)","answer":"Patients who gave a rating of 7 or 8 (medium)","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"32":1,"33":1,"34":1,"35":1,"36":1,"37":1,"38":1,"39":1,"41":1,"43":1,"47":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_HSP_RATING_9_10":{"id":"H_HSP_RATING_9_10","question":"Patients who gave their hospital a rating of 9 or 10 on a scale from 0 (lowest) to 10 (highest)","answer":"Patients who gave a rating of 9 or 10 (high)","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"32":1,"39":1,"40":1,"41":1,"43":1,"44":1,"45":1,"46":1,"47":1,"48":1,"49":1,"50":1,"51":1,"52":1,"53":1,"54":1,"55":1,"56":1,"57":1,"58":1,"59":1,"60":1,"61":1,"62":1,"63":1,"64":1,"65":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"100":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_HSP_RATING_LINEAR_SCORE":{"id":"H_HSP_RATING_LINEAR_SCORE","question":"Overall hospital rating - linear mean score","answer":"Overall hospital rating - linear mean score","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"70":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"97":1,"98":1,"":1}},"H_HSP_RATING_STAR_RATING":{"id":"H_HSP_RATING_STAR_RATING","question":"Overall hospital rating - star rating","answer":"Overall hospital rating - star rating","patientSurveyStarRating":{"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_RECMND":{"H_RECMND_DN":{"id":"H_RECMND_DN","question":"Patients who reported NO they would probably not or definitely not recommend the hospital","answer":"NO patients would not recommend the hospital (they probably would not or definitely would not recommend it)","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"27":1,"28":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_RECMND_DY":{"id":"H_RECMND_DY","question":"Patients who reported YES they would definitely recommend the hospital","answer":"YES patients would definitely recommend the hospital","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"23":1,"36":1,"37":1,"38":1,"39":1,"40":1,"41":1,"42":1,"43":1,"44":1,"45":1,"46":1,"47":1,"48":1,"49":1,"50":1,"51":1,"52":1,"53":1,"54":1,"55":1,"56":1,"57":1,"58":1,"59":1,"60":1,"61":1,"62":1,"63":1,"64":1,"65":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"97":1,"98":1,"99":1,"100":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_RECMND_PY":{"id":"H_RECMND_PY","question":"Patients who reported YES they would probably recommend the hospital","answer":"YES patients would probably recommend the hospital","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"0":1,"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"6":1,"7":1,"8":1,"9":1,"10":1,"11":1,"12":1,"13":1,"14":1,"15":1,"16":1,"17":1,"18":1,"19":1,"20":1,"21":1,"22":1,"23":1,"24":1,"25":1,"26":1,"27":1,"28":1,"29":1,"30":1,"31":1,"32":1,"33":1,"34":1,"35":1,"36":1,"37":1,"38":1,"39":1,"40":1,"41":1,"42":1,"43":1,"44":1,"45":1,"47":1,"49":1,"50":1,"53":1,"55":1,"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}},"H_RECMND_LINEAR_SCORE":{"id":"H_RECMND_LINEAR_SCORE","question":"Recommend hospital - linear mean score","answer":"Recommend hospital - linear mean score","patientSurveyStarRating":{"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"65":1,"66":1,"67":1,"68":1,"69":1,"70":1,"71":1,"72":1,"73":1,"74":1,"75":1,"76":1,"77":1,"78":1,"79":1,"80":1,"81":1,"82":1,"83":1,"84":1,"85":1,"86":1,"87":1,"88":1,"89":1,"90":1,"91":1,"92":1,"93":1,"94":1,"95":1,"96":1,"97":1,"98":1,"99":1,"":1}},"H_RECMND_STAR_RATING":{"id":"H_RECMND_STAR_RATING","question":"Recommend hospital - star rating","answer":"Recommend hospital - star rating","patientSurveyStarRating":{"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}},"H_STAR_RATING":{"H_STAR_RATING":{"id":"H_STAR_RATING","question":"Summary star rating","answer":"Summary star rating","patientSurveyStarRating":{"1":1,"2":1,"3":1,"4":1,"5":1,"":1},"hcahpsAnswerPercent":{"":1},"hcahpsLinearMeanValue":{"":1}}}}